Rhoades mss., LMC 2063
Lilly Library
- Editorial boards
  - Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences
    - Prensky, Wolf, Dale M. Steffensen, and W. L. Hughes. The use of iodinated RNA for gene localization. (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Schlanger, Gladys and Ruth Sager. Localization of five antibiotic resistances at the subunit level in chloroplast ribosomes of Chlamydomonas. (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Schwartz, Drew. Gene controlled cytosine demethylation in the promoter region of the Ac transposable element in maize. (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Schwartz, Drew. On the control of embryonic development in maize (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Schwartz, Drew. On the tissue specific regulation of gene function: Pre-setting and erasure (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Schwartz, Drew. Regulation of the expression of the Adh genes in maize. (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Simon, Anne E. and Milton W. Taylor. High frequency mutation at the ademine phosphor-ribosyltransferase locus in CHO cells due to deletion of the gene. (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Steffensen, Dale M. and D. E. Wimber. Localization of tRHA genes in the salivary chromosomes of drosophila by RNA:DNA hybridization (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Strausberg, Robert L. and Ronald A. Butow. Gene conversion at the vari locus on yeast mitochondrial DNA (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Sun, N. C., C. R. Y. Sun, A. W. Hsie and R. W. Tennant. Selective growth of some rodent epithelial cells in a medium containing citrulline (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Surzycki, Stefan J. and N. W. Gillham. Organelle mutations and their expression in Chlamydomonas (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Surzycki, Stefan J. and David L. Schellenbager. Purification and characterization of a putative igma factor from Chlamydomonas reinhardi reinhardi (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Tischfield, Jay A. and John J. Trill. Genetic instability at the adenine phosphoribosyl transferase locus In mouse L cells (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Trofatter, James A., Stephen R. Dlouhy, William DeMyer, P. Michael Conneally, and M.E. Hodes. Pelizaeus-Merzbacher disease: Tight linkage to proteolopid protein (PLP) gene exon variant (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Van Winkle-Swift, Karen P. Mating-type control of zygospore germination in Chlamydomonas: evidence from the homothallic species, C. monoica (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - von Wettstein, D. The synaptinemal complex and four strand crossing over (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Watson, John C. and Stefan J. Surzycki. Extensive sequence homology in the DNA coding for elongation factor Tu from Escherichia coli and the Chlamydomonas reinhardi chloroplast (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Williams, Gene R., Alice S. Williams and S.A. George. Hybridization of leucyl-tRNA isoacceptors from green leaves with nuclear and chloroplast DNA (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Science
    - Includes critiques only (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Grants (Box 12, Folder 8-9)
  - American Cancer Society. Research in genetically induced mutations of cytoplasmic entities (plastids), 1946-1948 (Box 12, Folder 8-9)
- Jones patent (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Materials concerning patent on the method of producing hybrid seed corn secured by Donald Jones. (Box 12, Folder 10)
- McClintock
  Materials pertaining to Barbara McClintock including papers concerning awards, correspondence with Rhoades, research and writings, etc. (see also: General Correspondence: 1942, Jan 13, Randolph to Rhoades; Editorial boards: PNAS, Drets and Shaw article)
  - Awards
    (Includes letters and printed materials)
    - Kimber award, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Lasker award, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - MacArthur Foundation Prize Fellow, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - National Medal of Science, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Nobel Prize, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Wolf Prize, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Biographical (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1935-1989 (Box 12, Folder 18-22)
  - Demonstrations (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Lectures, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Lecturescytogenetics, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Writings
    - Annual report, 1947-1948 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - The AC locus, Part I, March, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Chromosome organization and genic expression, June 1951 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Control of gene action in maize (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - The Ds locus, Part III, April, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Memorandum to Marcus Rhoades. First Section, Jan., 1949 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - The origin and location of transposed Ds 4710 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Translocation (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Printed (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Photographs
  - Five group photos (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Group photo (Box 13)
- Printed
  - Printed materials (Box 12, Folder 36)